I could do a workout with these boxes because the whole outfit weights over 5kg.
It's a silicone catsuit and I've never worn something like this before.
But let's stop talking and I'm going to unpack this one so we can see it.
Oh, it's super heavy.
This catsuit is like 4kg.
You always see latex, PVC, wet look, faux leather and I think I can call myself
something of an expert when it comes to alternative fashion.
but I've never seen or felt something like this before. The gauge of the material itself is 4
millimeter and with the weight it's like 10 times as heavy and as thick as your usual latex catsuit.
It's way softer than latex and also a bit more squishy. The brand is called Smithieson and I'll
tell you more about it later because now I will try to get into this one for the first time.
By the way, did I mention that it's a neck entry catsuit?
It's a neck entry catsuit. I have to squeeze my whole body through this hole.
So I decided to go with water-based lubricant and I'm going to put it on my feet
because they're mostly the hardest part to get into any catsuit.
Actually, I'm a bit nervous.
It reminds me a bit of like putting on neoprene though
because it's the thickness that is similar. And as it's so heavy it slides down again immediately.
Oh my god this feels so funny. I think I have to like pull it up to my hips and then get the
remaining material up. Again the weight works against me. I feel like the hardest part is done.
Maybe, I don't know. Okay I'm trying to think about doing the arms and I think it's going to be like a mess
but I'm going to coat my arms in lube.
Things I would have thought I'll never say.
I'll coat my arms in lube.
It's cold and wet.
But I hope that I can just like slip.
Slip it on now.
Oh my god, it's heavy.
First arm!
Oh here it is.
Alright I admit, I had help for the last 5cm but that was hard to get it over the shoulders.
Would have needed to use more loop.
I'm trying to like distribute the fabric a bit more is it fabric it's not fabric it's silicon
more lube on the inside or on my back and shoulders probably I can try to
pull it away from my body so it can settle in a better place
Now it's time to shine it up and I am using Vivishine here because they recommended it to me
for shining it up but you should wash it off after wearing it immediately and store it with talcum
but Smithies then is also launching their own shiner for these kind of suits which you don't
have to wash off after wearing it and of course I will link you the whole shop in
the comments so you can have a look yourself. Alright and now I need shoes. I
can tell you already that it's like it's really comfy so it's stretchy. The only
thing I can't move really well are like lifting the arms up more than that but
for the legs it's great. Let me have a look in the mirror. Yay! I think it looks
way better worn than not worn obviously and what I didn't tell you yet is that
it's one size so it fits like most people and it's not only one size but
it's also all gender but I think I am the first woman wearing a catsuit like
this at least I have not seen anyone else. Size wise it's recommended for
people from 60 to 100 kilo and I am on the lower end of that range with my 57
kilo and I think since I'm on the lower range it still looks really cool I did
think it would be bigger on me it's not really stretched by now so if you're a
bigger size than me I think it will stretch a lot more and also get a bit
thinner in the process I noticed that there is kind of a pre butt shape and
also for calf so it is a bit form on the booty and I think you can see that it
looks really good and that's actually the only part where I noticed that it's
a bit too wide so I can feel like air bubbles around here moving a bit but
otherwise it fits really snug it sits really tight and I'm happy that it fits
so good thanks to Smidison for sending this along I saw it online and I thought
wow I would love to try this and I've only seen it on guys on the pictures but
as you can see you can still wear it as a woman I actually wrote them and asked
hey do you think I as a woman can wear it and they said yes sure and send it to me.
They make lots of fun stuff. They're basically a gay fetish brand and have lots of puppy masks,
dragon hoods and a lot of other suits which are really really unique and I thought I saw
everything already but I didn't when I had a look at their homepage. So if you're brave enough
Check it out. I also have a discount code
So if you want to use that and found something on their home page, I will link it in the description text
Of course, I'll also take some pictures now with the suit. I think it's really really nice because
Unlike with latex you have no seams anywhere. So it's really
molded out of one piece so to say
part of this ensemble is also a mask in this case no eye openings and just a mouth opening
it's actually a bit too big for me also I can't put it on now because I would ruin my makeup
you've seen the amount of lube I put on my arms I can't do it with my face I simply put it on that
styrofoam hat and it is one size again so I think typical man's hat circumference 58 60 centimeter
that will be a fit mine is way smaller so you just have to like imagine that up here
as for taking it off again what I will do is I'll get under the shower and take it off with the
water because it works for latex so I hope it will also be easy that way to get out of this one
and since I have to remove and wash off the Vivishine anyway there's two in one and for
storing I'll just use talcum powder and then store it loosely. Does any one of you already
own a silicone catsuit or silicone pieces? I'm really curious because for me it was something
completely new and thanks again for Smitherson for sending this along it was
really a super cool experience I enjoyed it very much I'm glad that I could show
you something new here on my channel and I hope you enjoyed watching it and are
as curious as I am so check out the shop and check out my other videos if you
want to see other outfits and me just doing stupid stuff anyway thanks for
watching leave a thumbs up subscribe to my channel check out my socials and my
other pages and I will see you in the next video have a nice day bye